dayoftheweek.org 2019-12-24

# What Day Of The Week: Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Quick Link: [Click here __](https://www.dayoftheweek.org/privacy-opt-out.php)to opt-out and delete cookies.

**Effective August 8, 2018**

Thank you for choosing to be part of our community. We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy.

We are **Mavicus I.T. Solutions** (“company”, “we”, “us”, or “our”), a business registered in the Philippines.

Our address is 491 Kawayan Road, Brgy. Tugatog, Orani, Bataan 2112, Philippines.

### Introduction

We take your privacy very seriously. We seek to explain to you in the clearest way possible what information we collect, how we process it, and what rights you have in relation to it. If there are any terms in this Privacy Policy that you do not agree with please discontinue using the Services.

Our Privacy Policy is not just an exercise in complying with the law, but a continuation of our respect for you and your personal information. We undertake to preserve the confidentiality of all information you provide to us, and hope that you reciprocate.

Our Privacy Policy complies with the requirements of the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

GDPR requires us to tell you about your rights and our obligations to you in regards to the processing and control of your personal data. We do this now, by requesting that you read the information provided at [Know Your Privacy Rights __](http://www.knowyourprivacyrights.org/)website.

We also encourage you to read our **[Terms of Service __](https://www.dayoftheweek.org/terms.php)**. It contains important limitations on our liability to you when you use the Services.

**Please read this Privacy Policy carefully as it will help you make informed decision about sharing your personal information with us.**

This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected through our websites (“ **Sites** ”), mobile applications (“ **Apps** ”), and/or any related services, sales, marketing, or events. We refer to them collectively in this Privacy Policy as “ **Services** ”.

When you visit our Sites, use our Apps, or use the Services in general, we process any information that we collect from you, or that you provide to us. It covers information that could identify you (“ **personal information** ”) and information that could not. In the context of the law and this Privacy Policy, “ **process** ” means collect, store, transfer, use, or otherwise act on information.

Except as set out below, we do not share, sell, or disclose to a third party, any information collected through the Services.

### 1\. Data we process

We may collect, use, store, and transfer different kinds of personal data about you. We have collated these into groups as follows:

**Your identity** includes information such as first name or nickname, date of birth, and other identifiers that you may have provided at some time.

**Your contact information** includes information such as location, email address, and any other information you have given to us for the purpose of communication.

**Transaction data** includes details about payments or communications to and from you and information about products and services you have purchased from us.

**Technical data** includes you internet protocol (IP) address, browser type and version, time zone setting, geo-location (GPS), browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform, and other technology on the devices you use to access the Services.

**Marketing data** includes your preferences in receiving marketing from us, communication preferences, responses, and actions in relation to your use of the Services.

**Social media data** includes social media account details like your Facebook or Twitter logins, name, email address, friends list, profile picture, as well as other information you choose to make public.

We may aggregate anonymous data such as statistical or demographic data for any purpose. **Anonymous data** is data that does not identify you as an individual. **Aggregated data** may be derived from your personal data but is not considered personal information in law because it does not reveal your identity.

For example, we may aggregate profile data to assess interest in a product or service.

However, if we combine or connect aggregated data with your personal information so that it can identify you in any way, we treat the combined data as personal information and it will be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### 2\. If you do not provide personal information we need

Where we need to collect personal data by law, or under the terms of a contract we have with you, and you fail to provide that data when requested, we may not be able to perform that contract. In that case, we may have to stop providing the Services to you. If so, we will notify you of this at the time.

## The bases on which we process information about you

Privacy laws require us to determine under which of six defined bases we process different categories of your personal information, and to notify you of the basis for each category.

If a basis on which we process your personal information is no longer relevant then we shall immediately stop processing your data.

If the basis changes then if required by law we shall notify you of the change and of any new basis under which we have determined that we can continue to process your information.

### 3\. Information we process because we have a contractual obligation with you

When you interact with the Services like browsing our Sites, using our Apps, buying any product from us, or otherwise agree to our terms and conditions, a contract is formed between you and us.

In order to carry out our obligations under that contract we must process the information you give us. Some of this information may be personal information.

We may use it in order to:

  * verify your identity for security purposes
  * sell products and services to you
  * provide you with our services
  * provide you with suggestions and advice on products, services, and how to obtain the most from using the Services

We process this information on the basis there is a contract between us, or that you have requested we use the information before we enter into a legal contract.

We shall continue to process this information until the contract between us ends or is terminated by either party under the terms of the contract.

### 4\. Information we process with your consent

Through certain actions when otherwise there is no contractual relationship between us, such as when you browse our Sites or ask us to provide you more information about our business, including our products and services, you provide your consent to us to process information that may be personal information.

Wherever possible, we aim to obtain your explicit consent to process this information, for example, by asking you to agree to our use of cookies.

If you have given us explicit permission to do so, we may from time to time pass your name and contact information to selected associates whom we consider may provide services or products you would find useful.

We continue to process your information on this basis until you withdraw your consent or it can be reasonably assumed that your consent no longer exists.

You may withdraw your consent at any time by instructing us at our [Contact Us __](https://www.dayoftheweek.org/contact.php)page. However, if you do so, you may not be able to use the Services further.

### 5\. Information we process for the purposes of legitimate interests

We may process information on the basis there is a legitimate interest, either to you or to us, of doing so.

Where we process your information on this basis, we do after having given careful consideration to:

  * whether the same objective could be achieved through other means
  * whether processing (or not processing) might cause you harm
  * whether you would expect us to process your data, and whether you would, in the round, consider it reasonable to do so

For example, we may process your data on this basis for the purposes of:

  * record-keeping for the proper and necessary administration of our business
  * responding to unsolicited communication from you to which we believe you would expect a response
  * protecting and asserting the legal rights of any party
  * insuring against or obtaining professional advice that is required to manage business risk
  * protecting your interests where we believe we have a duty to do so

### 6\. Information we process because we have a legal obligation

Sometimes, we must process your information in order to comply with a statutory obligation.

For example, we may be required to give information to legal authorities if they so request or if they have the proper authorization such as a search warrant or court order.

This may include your personal information.

## Specific uses of information you provide to us

### 7\. Information provided on the understanding that it will be shared with a third party

The Services allow you to customize our content with a view to that information being read, copied, downloaded, or used by other people.

Examples include:

  * providing a date to generate a Day of the Week page
  * providing a year to generate a full year calendar

In posting personal information, it is up to you to satisfy yourself about the privacy level of every person who might use it.

We do not specifically use this information except to allow it to be displayed or shared.

Once your information enters the public domain, we have no control over what any individual third party may do with it. We accept no responsibility for their actions at any time.

Provided your request is reasonable and there is no legal basis for us to retain it, then at our discretion we may agree to your request to delete personal information that you have posted. You can make a request by using our [Contact Us __](https://www.dayoftheweek.org/contact.php)page.

### 8\. Complaints regarding content on the Services

If you complain about any of the content on the Services, we shall investigate your complaint.

If we feel it is justified or if we believe the law requires us to do so, we shall correct or remove the content while we investigate.

If we think your complaint is vexatious or without any basis, we shall not correspond with you about it.

### 9\. Information relating to your method of payment

Payment information is never taken by us or transferred to us either through the Services or otherwise. Our employees and contractors never have access to it.

At the point of payment, you are transferred to a secure page of PayPal, Stripe, Apple Store In-App Payments, Google Play In-App Payments, or some other reputable payment service provider. That page may be branded to look like a page on our Sites or Apps, but it is not controlled by us.

### 10\. Communicating with us

When you contact us, whether by telephone, through the Services or by email, we collect the data you have given to us in order to reply with the information you need.

We record your request and our reply in order to increase the efficiency of our business.

We keep personally identifiable information associated with your message, such as your name and email address so as to be able to track our communications with you to provide a high quality service.

### 11\. Complaining

When we receive a complaint, we record all the information you have given to us.

We use that information to resolve your complaint.

If your complaint reasonably requires us to contact some other person, we may decide to give to that other person some of the information contained in your complaint. We do this as infrequently as possible, but it is a matter for our sole discretion as to whether we do give information, and if we do, what that information is.

We may also compile statistics showing information obtained from this source to assess the level of service we provide, but not in a way that could identify you or any other person.

## Use of information we collect through automated systems when you visit our website

### 12\. Cookies

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your device by your web browser when you visit any website. They allow information gathered on one web page to be stored until it is needed for use on another, allowing a website to provide you with a personalized experience and the website owner with statistics about how you use the website so that it can be improved.

Some cookies may last for a defined period of time, such as one day or until you close your browser. Others last indefinitely.

Your web browser should allow you to delete any cookie you choose. It also should allow you to prevent or limit their use.

The Sites use cookies. They are placed by software that operates on our servers, and by software operated by third parties whose services we use.

If you are in the European Economic Area (EEA), when you first visit the Sites, we ask you whether you wish us to use cookies. If you choose not to accept them, we shall not use them for your visit except to record that you have not consented to their use for any other purpose.

If you choose not to use cookies or you prevent their use through your browser settings, you will not be able to use all the functionality of the Sites.

We use cookies in the following ways:

  * to track how you use the Sites
  * to record your answers to web forms

### 13\. Personal identifiers from your browsing activity

Requests by your web browser to our servers for web pages and other content on the Sites are recorded.

We record information such as your geographical location, your Internet service provider and your IP address. We also record information about the software you are using to browse the Sites, such as the type of computer or device and the screen resolution.

We use this information in aggregate to assess the popularity of the web pages on the Sites and how we perform in providing content to you.

If combined with other information we know about you from previous visits, the data possibly could be used to identify you personally.

### 14\. Managing Cookies

Most web browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies and to delete cookies. The methods for doing so vary from browser to browser, and from version to version. You can however obtain up-to-date information about blocking and deleting cookies via these links:

Blocking all cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites. If you block cookies, you will not be able to use all the features on the Sites.

### 15\. Our use of re-marketing

Re-marketing involves placing a cookie on your device when you browse our Sites in order to be able to serve to you an advert for our products or services when you visit other websites or use other mobile apps.

We may use a third party to provide us with re-marketing services from time to time. If so, then if you have consented to our use of cookies, you may see advertisements for our products and services on other websites or mobile apps.

## Disclosure and sharing of your information

### 16\. Information we obtain from third parties

Although we do not disclose your personal information to any third party (except as set out in this policy), we sometimes receive data that is indirectly made up from your personal information from third parties whose services we use.

### 17\. Business Transfers

We may share or transfer your information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.

### 18\. Third party advertising

Third parties may advertise on the Services. In doing so, those parties, their agents or other companies working for them may use technology that automatically collects information about you when their advertisement is displayed on the Services.

They may also use other technology such as cookies or JavaScript to personalize the content of, and to measure the performance of their adverts.

We do not have control over these technologies or the data that these parties obtain. Accordingly, this Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of these third parties.

### 19\. Interest-based advertising (IBA)

Some of the advertisements you see on the Sites are customized based on predictions about your interests generated from your visits to different websites. This type of ad customization is sometimes called “online behavioral” or “interest-based” advertising. Such form of online advertising helps support the free content, products, and services you get online. You may opt-out from interest-based advertising by following the instructions on this [page __](https://www.dayoftheweek.org/privacy-opt-out.php).

### 20\. Credit reference

To assist in combating fraud, we share information with credit reference agencies, so far as it relates to clients or customers who instruct their credit card issuer to cancel payment to us without having first provided an acceptable reason to us and given us the opportunity to refund their money.

### 21\. Data may be processed outside the European Union

Data for the Services are hosted in the United States.

We may also use outsourced services in countries outside the European Union from time to time in other aspects of our business.

Accordingly data obtained within the UK or any other country could be processed outside the European Union.

## Control over your own information

### 22\. Removal of your information

Follow the instructions on our **[Privacy Opt-Out __](https://www.dayoftheweek.org/privacy-opt-out.php)**page to delete cookies including those set by third party partners.

If you wish us to remove personally identifiable information from the Services, you should contact us to make your request. You can make a request by using our [Contact Us __](https://www.dayoftheweek.org/contact.php)page.

This may limit the service we can provide to you.

### 23\. Verification of your information

When we receive any request to access, edit, or delete personal identifiable information we shall first take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access or otherwise taking any action. This is important to safeguard your information.

### 24\. Email newsletter and marketing subscription

Our email subscription list is double opt-in. You need to confirm your subscription before we can send you our newsletter and marketing materials. Your email address and any other information related to that email address is housed in our mailing database indefinitely, or until you unsubscribe. You can opt-out of receiving marketing-related emails by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link or following the instructions provided in any informational email we send.

## Other matters

### 25\. Use of the Services by children

We do not sell products or provide services for purchase by children, nor do we market to children.

If you are under 18 years of age, you may use the Services only with consent from a parent or guardian.

If you are under 13 years of age (or equivalent minimum age in your country), please do not send any data about yourself when using the Services. No one under the age of 13 may provide any personal data.

We collect data about all users and visitors regardless of age, and we anticipate that some of those users and visitors will be children.

Such child users and visitors will inevitably interact with the Services and will be subject to whatever on-site (or on-app) marketing they find, wherever they are residing.

### 26\. Encryption of data sent between us

We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) certificates to verify our identity to your browser and to encrypt any data you give us.

Whenever information is transferred between us, you can check that it is done so using SSL by looking for a closed padlock symbol or other trust mark in your browser’s URL bar or toolbar.

### 27\. Links to third-party websites

The Services may contain advertisements from third parties that are not affiliated with us and which may link to other websites, online services, or mobile applications. We cannot guarantee the safety and privacy of data you provide to any third parties. Any data collected by third parties is not covered by this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of any third parties, including other websites, services, or applications that may be linked to or from the Services. You should review the policies of such third parties and contact them directly to respond to your questions.

### 28\. Processing of “Do Not Track” signal

Some web browsers have “Do Not Track” (DNT) or similar features that allow you to tell each website you visit that you do not want your activities on that website tracked. At present, the Services do not respond to DNT signals and consequently, the Services will continue to collect information about you even if your browser’s DNT feature is activated. We are not responsible on how third party services we use process the DNT signal. 

### 29\. How you can complain

If you are not happy with our Privacy Policy or if you have any complaint then you should tell us.

If a dispute is not settled then we hope you will agree to attempt to resolve it by engaging in good faith with us in a process of mediation or arbitration.

### 30\. Retention period for personal data

Except as otherwise mentioned in this Privacy Policy, we keep your personal information only for as long as required by us:

  * to provide you with the services you have requested
  * to comply with other law, including for the period demanded by our tax authorities
  * to support a claim or defense in court

### 31\. Compliance with the law

Our Privacy Policy has been compiled so as to comply with the law of every country or legal jurisdiction in which we aim to do business. If you think it fails to satisfy the law of your jurisdiction, we would like to hear from you.

However, ultimately it is your choice as to whether you wish to use the Services.

### 32\. Review of this Privacy Policy

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time as necessary. The terms that apply to you are those posted here on our website on the day you use the Services. We advise you to print a copy for your records.

If you have any question regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at our [Contact Us __](https://www.dayoftheweek.org/contact.php)page or by post to:

**Mavicus I.T. Solutions**  
491 Kawayan Road  
Brgy. Tugatog  
Orani, Bataan 2112  
Philippines
